Guide to the King-Lui Wu Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
King-Lui Wu papers
1942-2001
MS 1842
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
241
89 folios, 17 boxes
65.6
The papers comprise project records documenting architectural work undertaken by King-Lui Wu from 1942 to 1991, professional materials generated and compiled during his practice as an architect and tenure as a faculty member at Yale University's School of Architecture (1945-1988), and a small amount of personal correspondence. Project records, documenting both built and unbuilt work, consist mostly of sketches and include such drawing types as plans, elevations, sections, and perspective renderings; few working drawings exist. Project records also include a small amount of other materials, such as correspondence with clients and contractors, contracts, specifications, and receipts. Represented in the collection are such projects as the National Museum of Modern Art (Seoul, Korea) Yale student Manuscript Club (New Haven, CT), Mount Bethel Baptist Church (New Haven, CT), the Bank of Memphis, Yali Middle School (Changsha, China), and numerous private residences and offices. Professional papers include correspondence generated and collected while at Yale University, research materials, information pertaining to professional engagements and activities, and lecture notes for teaching.
Wu, King-Lui
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Vivian Wu, 2005, 2012.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
Biographical / Historical
King-Lui Wu was born on March 25, 1918, in Guangzhou, China. He studied at Yale, and then earned both his bachelor's (1944) and master's (1945) degrees in architecture at Harvard. He returned to Yale to teach in 1945, where he remained on the faculty until 1988. During his tenure at Yale, Wu taught several celebrated architects, including the current dean of the Yale School of Architecture, Robert A.M. Stern. Wu used sabbaticals from Yale to teach at the University of Cambridge in England and Massachusetts Institute of Technology.
His writing was published in numerous periodicals, including Architectural Record, The Architectural Review, and Werk. Although much of his work was concentrated in New Haven, Connecticut, Wu designed buildings in various locations throughout the world, such as Seoul, Korea, Changsha, China, and Hong Kong. Some of his most notable projects include the Yali Middle School, the Museum for Modern Art in Seoul, Mount Bethel Missionary Baptist Church, and the Yale student Manuscript Club. His designs include residences, offices, churches, museums, restaurants, and schools.
Wu placed great emphasis on natural light as a governing principle in design. He explored the use of this, the "most noble of natural phenomena," in what was perhaps his most popular course at Yale: "Daylight and Architecture." He applied this principle to residential design when he collaborated with artist Josef Albers on the home of Benjamin Dupont in Woodbridge, Connecticut. This house had sealed windows with hinged panels beneath them to enable ventilation. Because ventilation occurred through the panels, Wu was able focus on the windows as sources of light, which gave him greater freedom of size and placement.
Scope and Contents
The papers comprise project records documenting architectural work undertaken by King-Lui Wu from 1942 to 1991, professional materials generated and compiled during his practice as an architect and tenure as a faculty member at Yale University's School of Architecture (1945-1988), and a small amount of personal correspondence. Project records, documenting both built and unbuilt work, consist mostly of sketches and include such drawing types as plans, elevations, sections, and perspective renderings; few working drawings exist. Project records also include a small amount of other materials, such as correspondence with clients and contractors, contracts, specifications, and receipts. Represented in the collection are such projects as the National Museum of Modern Art (Seoul, Korea) Yale student Manuscript Club (New Haven, CT), Mount Bethel Baptist Church (New Haven, CT), the Bank of Memphis, Yali Middle School (Changsha, China), and numerous private residences and offices. Professional papers include correspondence generated and collected while at Yale University, research materials, information pertaining to professional engagements and activities, and lecture notes for teaching.
Arrangement
The collections is arranged in three series: I. Project files,1942-1991. II. Professional papers, 1954-2000. III. Personal correspondence, 1960-1995.
Other Finding Aids
For a list of projects and the boxes in which project materials are located, please consult the Project Index.
List of projects in collection
Art Gallery, Korea
Artist's Products Center
Artist's Studio
Atwood, Ada W. residence, Bethany, CT
Bank of Memphis
Barbaresi and Son art house, Bronxville, NY
Barbaresi, Peter residence
Barr, Browne residence, Bethany, CT
Bergen, Robert residence
Borge, Viktor residence: addition, Southbury, CT
Borge, Viktor: music pavilion, Southbury, CT
Borge, Viktor: studio, Southbury, CT
Butler garage addition
Chaet, Bernard R.: workroom addition, Orange, CT
Chang, H. C. residence, Cape May, NJ
Chang, H. C.: shop, Cape May, NJ
Chao, Y. R. residence
Cheung residence
China maps and studies
Common School, Amherst, MA
Concord Hospital, Concord, MA
Creative Arts Workshop: addition/alteration/terrace, New Haven, CT
CPS School, Dahong Wang, China
Delgado, J. residence, New Haven, CT
Dormitory, China
DuPont, Benjamin residence and furniture details, Woodbridge, CT
Downey, John: bathroom addition, New Haven, CT
Far East Restaurant, New Haven, CT
Friedman, Molumphy and Olson: doctors' office, New Haven, CT
Friedman, Irving: summer residence
Gate Lodge
Gifford residence: alteration, Woods Hole, MA
Gimbet, Richard residence: addition, New Haven, CT
Gerald Hill Estates, Old Westbury, NY
Fan, George residence, Ossining, NY
Guttentag residence: addition, Long Island, NY
Gymnase
Harvard Athletic/Fitness Center
Highland Arms Restaurant, Winsted, CT
Hole, Frank residence, New Haven, CT
Hole, Frank: kitchen renovation
Hostel, G.
Hsiang Ya Medical Center
Hsu, T.C.: penthouse addition, New York, NY
Johnson, Paul H. residence, Old Lyme, CT
Kenzer residence, Southampton, NY
China land use/study diagrams
Leader Federal Bank Building, Memphis, TN
Leader Federal Bank Building, Lamar Branch
Loree, Mrs. Dean residence, Ann Arbor, MI
Mark Levinson Audio Systems, Hamden, CT
Kobak, S.J. residence, Old Westbury, NY
Morefar: Bath house, Brewster, NY
Morefar: Daylighted indoor tennis court, Brewster, NY
Morefar: Hsu, T.C. residence and furniture, Brewster, NY
Morefar: Storr, C.V. proposed golf house, pool house, and staff house
Mount Bethel Baptist Church, New Haven
Mueller, Adolph II, guest house
Museum, Taiwan
Nagata residence
National Museum of Modern Art, Seoul, Korea
New China Restaurant alterations, New Haven, CT
New Haven City Hall, New Haven, CT
Nims, Ellen residence, Woodbridge, CT
Norwood Estates, Norwood, MA
Ordin residence
Pencil Points, Pittsburgh
Pian, Ted residence, addition, Cambridge, MA
Plunkett, John residence, Hamden, CT
Police Headquarters on Parkway
Richeimer residence: addition, Orange, CT
Rickers, Maria residence, Storrs, CT
Rodetsky, Jack and Sue residence, MA
Roth, Herbert G., Fairfield, CT
Rouse, Irving and Mary residence and garage, North Haven, CT
Rouse: summer cottage
Rudnick, Dorothea residence, addition, alteration, New Haven, CT
S.C.D. competiton
Self-service market
Shangri-La, a home for the aged, Ann Arbor, MI
Stephenson, Frank residence, garage, workshop, Lyme, CT
Stoddard, C.F. Jr. residence
Suddard, Adrienne ("Vicky") residence, Killingworth, CT
Systems of Living Complex
Tang, S.C. residence, Hong Kong
Taylor, C.F. residence, Winchester, MA
Tse, Stephen residence, Brewster, NY
Tung, David residence, Rye, NY
Tung, H.H. residence, Rye, NY
Urban Housing Unit
Villa K.K.: addition
Wang Laboratories, Redding, MA
Wang, An: addition and alteration, Lincoln, MA
Webb, Dwight residence: addition, Westport, CT
Wheaton College Art Center
Wong, Andrew residence and furniture, Hamden, CT
Wrexham Foundation (Manuscript Society), Yale University, New Haven, CT
Wu, King-Lui and Vivian residence, Hamden, CT
Wu, Lundo residence: alterations
Yali Middle School, Changsha, China
Yu, Ling: garage addition, dressing and pool filter rooms, Kwanyin Temple
Art Gallery, Korea
Artist's Products Center
Artist's Studio
Atwood, Ada W. residence, Bethany, CT
Bank of Memphis
Barbaresi and Son art house, Bronxville, NY
Barbaresi, Peter residence
Barr, Browne residence, Bethany, CT
Bergen, Robert residence
Borge, Viktor residence: addition, Southbury, CT
Borge, Viktor: music pavilion, Southbury, CT
Borge, Viktor: studio, Southbury, CT
Butler garage addition
Chaet, Bernard R.: workroom addition, Orange, CT
Chang, H. C. residence, Cape May, NJ
Chang, H. C.: shop, Cape May, NJ
Chao, Y. R. residence
Cheung residence
China land use/study diagrams
China maps and studies
Common School, Amherst, MA
Concord Hospital, Concord, MA
Creative Arts Workshop: addition/alteration/terrace, New Haven, CT
CPS School, Dahong Wang, China
Delgado, J. residence, New Haven, CT
Dormitory, China
DuPont, Benjamin residence and furniture details, Woodbridge, CT
Downey, John: bathroom addition, New Haven, CT
Far East Restaurant, New Haven, CT
Friedman, Molumphy and Olson: doctors' office, New Haven, CT
Friedman, Irving: summer residence
Gate Lodge
Gifford residence: alteration, Woods Hole, MA
Gimbet, Richard residence: addition, New Haven, CT
Gerald Hill Estates, Old Westbury, NY
Fan, George residence, Ossining, NY
Guttentag residence: addition, Long Island, NY
Gymnase
Harvard Athletic/Fitness Center
Highland Arms Restaurant, Winsted, CT
Hole, Frank residence, New Haven, CT
Hole, Frank: kitchen renovation
Hostel, G.
Hsiang Ya Medical Center
Hsu, T.C.: penthouse addition, New York, NY
Johnson, Paul H. residence, Old Lyme, CT
Kenzer residence, Southampton, NY
Kobak, S.J. residence, Old Westbury, NY
Leader Federal Bank Building, Lamar Branch
Leader Federal Bank Building, Memphis, TN
Mark Levinson Audio Systems, Hamden, CT
Loree, Mrs. Dean residence, Ann Arbor, MI
Morefar: Bath house, Brewster, NY
Morefar: Daylighted indoor tennis court, Brewster, NY
Morefar: Hsu, T.C. residence and furniture, Brewster, NY
Morefar: Starr, C.V. proposed golf house, pool house, and staff house
Mount Bethel Baptist Church, New Haven
Mueller, Adolph II, guest house
Museum, Taiwan
Nagata residence
National Museum of Modern Art, Seoul, Korea
New China Restaurant alterations, New Haven, CT
New Haven City Hall, New Haven, CT
Nims, Ellen residence, Woodbridge, CT
Norwood Estates, Norwood, MA
Oldrin residence
Pencil Points, Pittsburgh
Pian, Ted residence, addition, Cambridge, MA
Plunkett, John residence, Hamden, CT
Police Headquarters on Parkway
Richeimer residence: addition, Orange, CT
Rickers, Maria residence, Storrs, CT
Rodetsky, Jack and Sue residence, MA
Roth, Herbert G., Fairfield, CT
Rouse, Irving and Mary residence and garage, North Haven, CT
Rouse: summer cottage
Rudnick, Dorothea residence, addition, alteration, New Haven, CT
S.C.D. competiton
Self-service market
Shangri-La, a home for the aged, Ann Arbor, MI
Stephenson, Frank residence, garage, workshop, Lyme, CT
Stoddard, C.F. Jr. residence
Suddard, Adrienne ("Vicky") residence, Killingworth, CT
Systems of Living Complex
Tang, S.C. residence, Hong Kong
Taylor, C.F. residence, Winchester, MA
Tse, Stephen residence, Brewster, NY
Tung, David residence, Rye, NY
Tung, H.H. residence, Rye, NY
Urban Housing Unit
Villa K.K.: addition
Wang Laboratories, Redding, MA
Wang, An: addition and alteration, Lincoln, MA
Webb, Dwight residence: addition, Westport, CT
Wheaton College Art Center
Wong, Andrew residence and furniture, Hamden, CT
Wrexham Foundation (Manuscript Society), Yale University, New Haven, CT
Wu, King-Lui and Vivian residence, Hamden, CT
Wu, Lundo residence: alterations
Yali Middle School, Changsha, China
Yu, Ling: garage addition, dressing and pool filter rooms, Kwanyin Temple
Archaeological Research Center, Copan, Honduras
Boston Museum of Fine Arts furniture exhibit
Carlyle residence
Clarke residence
Druid Hills Country Club
Fan, George residence, Ossining, NY
Hayden residence, Milford, CT
Hill, Gerald estates, Old Westbury, CT
Architecture, Domestic -- Connecticut -- 20th Century; Architecture, Domestic -- New York (State) -- 20th Century; Daylighting; Light in architecture; Albers, Josef, 1888-1976; Wrexham Foundation, Inc; Yale University. School of Art and Architecture. Dept. of Architecture; Yale University -- Faculty
- Project files, 1942-1991; Series I
  Other Finding Aids
  For a list of projects and the boxes in which project materials are located, please consult the Project Index.
  - An Artist's Products Center
    - Drawings (Folder 46)
  - An Artist's Studio (Academic Project)
    - Drawings (Folder 86)
  - Apartment building (unidentifiable): plans, sections, elevations, site plan
    - Drawings (Box 90, Folder 84)
  - Archaeological Research Center
    Scope and Contents
    Job location: Copan, Honduras
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 90)
  - Atwood, Ada W., 1955
    Job location: Bethany, CT
    - Drawings (Folder 56)
  - Bank of Memphis (unbuilt)
    - Drawings (Folder 57)
  - Barbaresi and Son: Proposed Art House
    Job location: Bronxville, NY
    - Drawings (Folder 56)
  - Barbaresi, Mr. and Mrs. Peter: Proposed Residence, 1954
    - Drawings (Folder 56)
  - Barr, Browne: Residence, 1958
    - Drawings (Box 9, Folder 19, Folder 28)
    - Photographs (Box 93, Box 97)
  - Bath House
    - Drawings (Folder 77)
  - Bergen, Dr. and Mrs. Robert: Proposed Residence, 1971
    - Drawings (Folder 36)
  - Borge, Mr. and Mrs.: Addition, Alteration, 1958
    Job location: Southbury, CT
    - Drawings (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Boston Museum of Fine Arts furniture exhibit, 1995
    Job location: Boston, MA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 90)
  - Butler, Mr.: Garage Addition
    - Drawings (Folder 12)
  - Carlyle (?): Residence
    - Drawings (Box 90)
  - Chaet, Mr. Bernard R.: Workroom addition, 1955
    Job location: Orange, CT
    - Drawings (Folder 51)
  - Chang, Mr. and Mrs. C.H.: Shop, Residence, 1955; 1971
    Job location: Cape May, NJ
    - Drawings (Box 9, Folder 35, Folder 53)
  - Chao, Dr. and Mrs. Y.R.: Residence, 1972
    - Drawings (Box 90, Folder 32)
  - Cheung, Mr. and Mrs.: Proposed Residence, 1960
    - Drawings (Folder 56)
  - China maps and studies
    - Drawings (Folder 66, Folder 77, Folder 87)
  - China: Dormitory
    - Drawings (Folder 79)
  - Church (unbuilt?), 1985
    - Drawings (Box 90)
  - Clarke: Residence, 1985
    - Drawings (Box 90)
  - Common School (Proposed plan), 1968-1969
    Job location: Amherst, MA
    - Drawings (Folder 56)
  - Concord Hospital
    Job location: Concord, MA
    - Drawings (Folder 76)
  - CPS School, Dahong Wang (plans, sections, perspective views, detail drawings), 1942
    - Drawings (Folder 73)
  - Creative Arts Workshop (CAW) Terrace, Addition, 1977
    Job location: New Haven, CT
    - Drawings (Folder 14, Folder 64)
  - Daylight Sources (Alternative Sections)
    - Drawings (Folder 75)
  - Delgado, Dr. and Mrs. J.: Residence, 1959
    - Drawings (Folder 51)
  - Downey, Mr. and Mrs. John: New Bath, 1981
    - Drawings (Folder 39)
  - Druid Hills Country Club (Proposed)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 90)
  - DuPont, Mr. and Mrs. Benjamin B.: Residence, 1952-1957
    Job location: Woodbridge, CT
    - Drawings (Box 90, Box 93–94, Folder 9a, Folder 19, Folder 23, Folder 58, Folder 60)
    - Photographs (Box 90, Folder 24, Folder 43)
  - Fan, Dr. and Mrs. George J.: Residence, 1986-1989
    Job location: Ossining, NY
    - Drawings (Box 90, Folder 24, Folder 43)
  - Freidman, Dr. and Mrs.: Proposed Summer Home, 1972-1973
    - Drawings (Box 90, Folder 2, Folder 32)
  - Freidman, Molumphy and Olson, Drs.: Office, 1969
    - Drawings (Box 9, Box 90, Folder 2, Folder 35)
  - Furniture sketches
    - Drawings (Box 92, Folder 38)
  - Gate Lodge (Academic Project)
    - Drawings (Folder 86)
  - Gifford, Mr. and Mrs.: Alteration at Woods Hole
    - Drawings (Folder 24)
  - Gimbet, Col. And Mrs. Richard: New Room, 1968
    - Drawings (Folder 56)
  - Guttentag House: Addition, 1970
    Job location: Long Island, NY
    - Drawings (Folder 39)
  - Gymnase
    - Drawings (Folder 77)
  - Harvard Athletic Fitness Center, 1986
    - Drawings (Folder 7, Folder 65)
  - Hayden Residence, 1957
    Job location: Milford, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 90)
  - Highland Arms Restaurant, 1956
    Job location: Winsted, CT
    - Drawings (Folder 58, Folder 65)
  - Hill, Gerald: Estates
    Job location: Old Westbury, CT
    - Drawings (Folder 30)
  - Hole, Prof. and Mrs. Frank: Addition, 1983; 1985
    - Drawings (Box 90, Folder 34)
  - Hostel, G.: (plans, sections, elevations)
    - Drawings (Folder 74)
  - Housing drawings of typical units (plans/sections/ elevations)
    - Drawings (Folder 1)
  - Hsiang Ya Medical Center
    - Drawings (Folder 85)
  - Hsu, T.C.: House [at Morefar], 1970
    Job location: Brewster, MA
    - Drawings (Box 97, Folder 20, Folder 33)
    - Photographs (Box 97)
  - Hsu, T.C.: Penthouse addition
    Job location: New York, NY
    - Drawings (Box 90, Folder 33)
  - Johnson, Mr. Paul: Residence, 1963
    Job location: Old Lyme, CT
    - Drawings (Box 9, Box 90, Folder 18–19, Folder 40)
    - Photographs (Box 97, Box 99)
  - Kenzer, Mr. and Mrs.: Residence, 1970-1971
    Job location: Long Island, Southampton, NY
    - Drawings (Box 9, Folder 36, Folder 56)
  - Kobak, Mr. and Mrs. S.J.: Residence
    Job location: Old Westbury, Long Island, NY
    - Drawings (Box 90, Folder 30, Folder 78)
  - Korea Museum of Modern Art (daylight consultant), 1983
    - Drawings (Box 90, Folder 6, Folder 64, Folder 78, Folder 83)
  - Land use / Study Diagrams (post war China)
    - Drawings (Folder 46)
  - Leader Federal Bank Building
    Job location: Memphis, TN
    - Drawings (Folder 16)
  - Leader Federal Bank Building, Lamar Branch, 1959
    - Drawings (Folder 16)
  - Library / Dormitory Drawings
    - Drawings (Folder 81)
  - Loree, Mrs. Dean: Residence
    Job location: Ann Arbor, MI
    - Drawings (Folder 63)
  - Manuscript Society House (Wrexham Foundation Inc.), 1961
    - Drawings (Box 9, Folder 8, Folder 28, Folder 63–64)
  - Mark Levinson Audio Systems, 1978
    Job location: Hamden, Fair Haven, CT
    - Drawings (Folder 48)
  - Morefar (bath house, golf house, staff house, daylighted indoor tennis court)
    - Drawings (Box 9, Box 90, Folder 37, Folder 41)
  - Mt. Bethel Baptist Church, 1971-1972
    - Drawings (Box 9, Box 94, Folder 13, Folder 19, Folder 64)
    - Photographs (Box 94, Box 97)
  - Mueller, Mr. and Mrs. Adolph, II: Proposed Guest House, 1991
    - Drawings (Folder 27)
  - Museum, Taiwan (unbuilt)
    - Drawings (Box 90, Folder 57)
  - Nagata, Mr. and Mrs.: Residence
    - Drawings (Folder 18)
  - New China Restaurant, 1949-1950
    - Drawings (Folder 5, Folder 44)
    - Photographs (Box 97)
  - New Haven City Hall [conserved rendering]
    - Drawings (Folder 88)
  - Nims, Ms. Ellen
    - Drawings (Folder 56)
  - Norwood Estates
    Job location: Norwood, MA
    - Drawings (Folder 64)
  - Oldrin Residence (sketches + drawings)
    - Drawings (Folder 31)
  - Pencil Points, Pittsburgh (Architectural Competition)
    Job location: Pittsburgh, PA
    - Drawings (Folder 81)
  - PH (basic site layout, perspective views, elevations)
    - Drawings (Folder 74, Folder 84)
  - Pian, Prof. and Mrs. Ted.: Addition, 1979
    Job location: Cambridge, MA
    - Drawings (Box 90, Folder 10, Folder 20, Folder 32)
  - Plunkett, Dr. and Mrs. John: Residence, 1953
    Job location: Hamden, CT
    - Drawings (Folder 51, Folder 61)
  - Police Headquarters on Parkway (Academic Project)
    - Drawings (Folder 86)
  - Richeimer, Mr. and Mrs.: Addition, 1979
    - Drawings (Folder 39)
  - Rickers, Dr. Maria: Residence, 1955
    Job location: Storrs, CT
    - Drawings (Box 9, Box 94, Folder 54)
    - Photographs (Box 94, Box 97)
  - Rodetsky, Mr. and Mrs. Jack and Sue: Residence, 1979
    - Drawings (Folder 24)
  - Roth, Mr. and Mrs. Herbert G.: Residence, 1955
    Job location: Fairfield, CT
    - Drawings (Folder 51)
  - Rouse, Irving and Mary: House, 1952-1953
    Job location: North Haven, CT
    - Drawings (Box 9, Box 97, Folder 44, Folder 47, Folder 62, Folder 67)
    - Photographs (Box 95, Box 97)
  - Rouse, Professor: Summer Cottage, 1966
    - Drawings (Folder 47)
  - Rudnick, Dorothea: Residence (drawings), 1972; 1956
    Job location: Hamden, New Haven, CT
    - Drawings (Box 9, Box 97–98, Folder 18–19, Folder 28, Folder 32, Folder 54)
    - Photographs (Box 95, Box 97–98)
  - S.C.D. Competition Drawings
    - Drawings (Folder 67)
  - Self-Service Market (Academic Project)
    - Drawings (Folder 86)
  - Shangri-La', A home for the Aged (Academic Project)
    - Drawings (Folder 86)
  - Stephenson, Frank: Residence (drawings), 1960
    Job location: Lyme, CT
    - Drawings (Box 9, Box 90, Folder 23, Folder 55)
  - Stoddard, Mr. and Mrs. C.F., Jr.: Proposed Residence
    - Drawings (Folder 56)
  - Starr, Mr. C.V. (Morefar), 1968
    - Drawings (Folder 12, Folder 20)
  - Student Projects
    - Drawings (Folder 59)
  - Suddard, Ms. Adrienne V.: Residence, 1965
    Job location: Killingworth, CT
    - Drawings (Box 9, Box 91, Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Photographs (Box 98–99)
  - Swatow China Finance Center, 1986
    - Drawings (Box 91)
  - Systems of Living Complex (Housing type study)
    - Drawings (Folder 81)
  - Tang, Mr. and Mrs. S.C.: Proposed Residence, 1960
    Job location: Hong Kong
    - Drawings (Box 9, Folder 41, Folder 56)
  - Taylor, Prof. and Mrs. C.F.: Residence
    Job location: Winchester, CT
    - Drawings (Folder 69)
  - The Far East Restaurant, 1952-1959
    - Drawings (Box 9, Folder 5, Folder 44)
    - Photographs (Box 97)
  - Topographical plan of land in Lexington, MA, 1955
    Job location: Lexington, MA
    - Drawings (Folder 56)
  - TSD (plans)
    - Drawings (Folder 73)
  - Tse, Mr. and Mrs. Stephen: Residence
    - Drawings (Box 91, Folder 80)
    - Photographs (Box 98)
  - Tung, Dr. and Mrs. David: Residence, 1959
    Job location: Rye, NY
    - Drawings (Box 91, Folder 9b, Folder 45)
    - Photographs (Box 96, Box 98)
  - Tung, H.H.: Residence
    - Drawings (Box 9, Folder 19, Folder 28)
  - Unidentied projects, 1943
    - Drawings (Box 91, Folder 70–72, Folder 74, Folder 81–84)
  - Unidentified detail drawings
    - Drawings (Folder 68)
  - Unidentified blueprints
    - Drawings (Folder 23)
  - Unidentified drawings, 1986-1989
    - Drawings (Folder 25–26, Folder 30, Folder 32, Folder 42, Folder 44, Folder 50)
  - Unidentified housing
    - Drawings (Box 90, Folder 49, Folder 63, Folder 82)
    - Photographs (Box 98–99)
  - Unidentified perspective views
    - Drawings (Folder 28)
  - Unidentified rendered views
    - Drawings (Folder 17–18)
  - Unidentified sketches
    - Drawings (Box 92, Folder 15, Folder 22, Folder 36–38, Folder 57)
  - Unidentified views
    - Drawings (Folder 19)
  - Unidentified window details
    - Drawings (Folder 50)
  - Unidentified perspective sketches
    - Drawings (Folder 68)
  - Unidentified plans and elevations [high school?]
    - Drawings (Folder 89)
  - Unidentified window details and sections
    - Drawings (Folder 11)